<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Center for Security, Theory and Algorithmic Research on CSTAR | IIIT Hyderabad</title>
    <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Center for Security, Theory and Algorithmic Research on CSTAR | IIIT Hyderabad</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 17:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to store a graph?</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/how_to_store_a_graph/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/how_to_store_a_graph/</guid>
      <description>Abstract How does one store a graph in the database? Typically the vertices are labelled by a set {1, 2, &amp;hellip;, n}. The edges can be denoted in many different ways: adjacency matrix, incidence matrix, adjacency list, to name a few. But what if the vertices are labelled in a more creative way, such that the labels of the vertices themselves denote their adjacencies? This eliminates the need for storing the edges!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying the border of depth-3 algebraic circuits</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/demystifying-the-border-of-depth-3-algebraic-circuits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/demystifying-the-border-of-depth-3-algebraic-circuits/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Border (or approximative) complexity of polynomials plays an integral role in GCT approach to P!=NP. This raises an important open question: can a border circuit be efficiently debordered (i.e. convert from approximative to exact)? Or, could the approximation involve exponential-precision which may not be efficiently simulatable? Circuits of depth 3 or 4, are a good testing ground for this question.
Recently, (Kumar ToCT&#39;20) proved the universal power of the border of top-fanin-2 depth-3 circuits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siddhartha Das</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/siddharthadas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/siddharthadas/</guid>
      <description>Testing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum weirdness in query-to-communication simulation and the role of symmetry</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/quantum-weirdness-in-query-to-communication-simulation-and-the-role-of-symmetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/quantum-weirdness-in-query-to-communication-simulation-and-the-role-of-symmetry/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Buhrman, Cleve and Wigderson (STOC&#39;98) showed that for every Boolean function $f : {0,1}^n \to {0,1}$ and $G \in {AND_2, XOR_2}$, the bounded-error quantum communication complexity of the composed function (f \circ G) equals O(Q(f) log n), where Q(f) denotes the bounded-error quantum query complexity of f. This is known as the BCW Simulation Theorem. This is in contrast with the classical setting, where it is easy to show that $R^{cc}(f \circ G) \leq 2R(f)$, where R^{cc} and R denote bounded-error communication and query complexity, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A(n almost) Universal Algorithm for Global Minimum Cut</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/an_almost_universal_algorithm_for_global_minimum_cut-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/an_almost_universal_algorithm_for_global_minimum_cut-copy/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Consider the following 2-respecting min-cut problem: Given a weighted graph G and its spanning tree T, find the minimum cut among the cuts that contain at most two edges in T. This problem is an important subroutine in Karger&amp;rsquo;s celebrated randomized near-linear-time min-cut algorithm [STOC&#39;96]. I will present a new approach for this problem which can be easily implemented in many settings, such as sequential, cut-query, streaming, PRAM, distributed CONGEST, and 2-party communication protocol, each achieving the state of the art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QBF Solving: Advantages and disadvantages of different approaches</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/qbf_solving_advantages_and_disadvantages_of_different_approaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/qbf_solving_advantages_and_disadvantages_of_different_approaches/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Boolean satisfiability (SAT) is believed to be hard in the worst case. However, many heuristic based software can solve industrial SAT instances with tens of thousands of variables in a reasonable amount of time. Theoretical study of these heuristics helps us in understanding the type of formulas these software can and can&amp;rsquo;t solve in polynomial time, and in comparing different software.
Motivated by the success of SAT solving software, software have been created for an even harder problem: checking whether a Quantified Boolean Formula (QBF) is true or false.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Quantum Computers Outperform Gradient Descent?</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/can_quantum_computers_outperform_gradient_descent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/can_quantum_computers_outperform_gradient_descent/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Gradient descent is a marvel of an algorithm that allows very efficient optimization in high-dimensional spaces. It was provably the best algorithm for well-structured optimization tasks. such as non-smooth convex optimization in large dimensions. But then came quantum computers with their fancy superpositions, pulling off amazing feats of computation. So questions of the form &amp;ldquo;Is this the best algorithm we have?&amp;rdquo; had to be asked all over again.
In this talk we will take a look at gradient descent, at the task of non-smooth convex optimization, and we&amp;rsquo;ll show that quantum computers can&amp;rsquo;t improve upon gradient descent in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Functional Lower Bounds for Restricted Arithmetic Circuits of Depth Four</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/functional-lower-bounds-for-restricted-arithmetic-circuits-of-depth-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/functional-lower-bounds-for-restricted-arithmetic-circuits-of-depth-4/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: One of the major motivations to study Arithmetic/Algebraic Circuit Complexity was due to the “slow” progress in proving lower bounds in Boolean Circuit Complexity. Based on some empirical evidence, researchers believed that the power of underlying algebra and the possibility of cancellations could help understand computations on the algebraic setting.
In this talk we shall outline some of the connections between Boolean Circuit Complexity and Algebraic Circuit Complexity. In particular (by building upon some previous work [due to Yao, Beigel &amp;amp; Tarui, Forbes, Kumar &amp;amp; Saptharishi], we shall present a path towards proving stronger (nonuniform) ACC0 lower bounds via proving “functional” lower bounds in the algebraic setting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lower Bounds in Algebraic Circuit Complexity</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/lower_bounds_in_algebraic_circuit_complexity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/lower_bounds_in_algebraic_circuit_complexity/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Algebraic circuits and formulas are the standard computational models for computing multivariate polynomials. They are similar to boolean circuits and formulas except that in this case, gates are labelled by &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;x&amp;rsquo;. Another important model is that of an algebraic branching program (ABP), which is an intermediate model between circuits and formulas in terms of computational power. I will begin the talk by defining these models of computation formally, and then survey some of the results that have helped shape our understanding of algebraic circuits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shortest Paths in Time-varying Networks</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/shortest_paths_in_time_varying_networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/shortest_paths_in_time_varying_networks/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Suppose you are given the traffic situation on each road of your city and you want to find the quickest way to your workplace from your home. The city&amp;rsquo;s road network can be modelled by a graph whose edge weights represent the amount of traffic on the roads. Now the problem boils down to computing a shortest path in this graph, which can be solved by standard algorithms (Dijkstra&amp;rsquo;s algorithm, Bellman-Ford-Moore algorithm).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Quantum Science and Technology Symposium</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/nqsts-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/nqsts-event/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Algorithms &amp; Complexity</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/algorithms-complexity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/algorithms-complexity/</guid>
      <description>Algorithms are fundamental objects of study in computer science. They are not only the basic building blocks of the computational world around us, but algorithmic processes are ubiquitous in nature too. In this fast-paced world we are not only satisfied with solving a task, but we would like to solve them as fast as possible. The related area of Computational Complexity theory focuses on this issue of computational efficiency. That is, it aims to quantify the amount of computational resources required to solve a given task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distributed &amp; Parallel Computing</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/distributed-parallel-computing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/distributed-parallel-computing/</guid>
      <description>Research in parallel computing took off vigorously in the past two decades with the advent of multi-core and many-core architectures. There is now a renewed interest in designing and engineering efficient parallel algorithms targeted at a multitude of parallel architecture and platforms. Several problems from domains including graph algorithms, natural sciences, optimization, and machine learning are of particular interest owing to their wide range of applications.
Some of the fundamental outcomes of current generation research in parallel computing includes tools for analyzing and modeling GPU computations, techniques for optimizing GPU computations, engineering mechanisms to and algorithms that aim to overlap communication and computation, apart from a host of libraries, domain specific languages, and automatic compiler techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Girish Varma</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/girish.varma/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/girish.varma/</guid>
      <description>Testing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kannan Srinathan</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/kannansrinathan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/kannansrinathan/</guid>
      <description>Testing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pawan Kumar</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/pawankumar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/pawankumar/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Pawan Kumar is broadly interested in numerical algorithms with applications to machine learning, computer vision, signal processing. He joined the institute in 2017. Before joining IIIT, Hyderabad, he had his PhD from INRIA, France, and has done several postdocs in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security &amp; Privacy</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/security-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/security-privacy/</guid>
      <description>Computer security or cybersecurity is the protection of cyber systems and computer networks from the disclosure of information, damage to physical and virtual infrastructure, electronic data, as well as from interruption of the services they provide. The cybersecurity field is becoming important because of the growing dependence on computers, the Internet, wireless communications standards (e.g., Bluetooth and Wi-Fi), as well as the increasing number of &amp;ldquo;smart&amp;rdquo; IoT devices. Due to a variety of reasons, cybersecurity has become one of the major challenges of the modern IT age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shatrunjay Rawat</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/shatrunjayrawat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/shatrunjayrawat/</guid>
      <description>Testing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Student</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/students/student/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/students/student/</guid>
      <description>Testing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theory for Machine Learning</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/theory-for-ml/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/theory-for-ml/</guid>
      <description>In this group, we are interested in theoretical aspects of algorithms that relate specifically to machine learning and related domains such as vision. Some of the research problems consist of designing of better optimization models, solvers and provable guarantee of convergence. Learning part of machine learning often corresponds to minimizing a suitable loss function defined for a labelled data. Hence, optimization methods lies at the center of machine learning research in theory and algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Algorithmizing the Multiplicity Schwartz-Zippel Lemma</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/algorithmizing_the_multiplicity_schwartz-zippel_lemma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/algorithmizing_the_multiplicity_schwartz-zippel_lemma/</guid>
      <description>Abstract The degree maxim states that any non-zero univariate polynomial of degree at most d has at most d roots (counted with multiplicity). A generalization of this to the multivariate setting, proved by Dvir-Kopparty-Saraf-Sudan asserts that over any field, a low-degree polynomial cannot vanish with high multiplicity very often on a sufficiently large product set. It has found numerous applications; in particular, in the definition and properties of multiplicity codes by Kopparty-Saraf-Yekhanin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ankit Gangwal</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/ankitgangwal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/ankitgangwal/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Ankit Gangwal is an Assistant Professor at IIIT Hyderabad, India. He has worked in different mainstream areas of research, including distributed ledger technology (blockchain and cryptocurrencies), networking (ICN and SDN), and AI (GAN-based password cracking). However, the main theme of his research has always been security and privacy. His research work is multidisciplinary. Currently, He is focusing on Blockchain-, Privacy-, and Security-related research areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashok Kumar Das</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/ashokdas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/ashokdas/</guid>
      <description>Ashok Kumar Das received a Ph.D. degree in computer science and engineering, an M.Tech. degree in computer science and data processing, and an M.Sc. degree in mathematics and computing from IIT Kharagpur, India. He is currently an Associate Professor with the Center for Security, Theory and Algorithmic Research, International Institute of Information Technology, Hyderabad, India. His current research interests include cryptography, network security, security in vehicular ad hoc networks, smart grids, smart homes, Internet of Things (IoT), Internet of Drones, Internet of Vehicles, Cyber-Physical Systems (CPS) and cloud computing, intrusion detection, blockchain and AI/ML security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CQST Inagurated</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/news/cqst-inagurated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/news/cqst-inagurated/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distributed Point Functions meet Secure Multiparty Computation</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/distributed_point_functions_meet_secure_multiparty_computation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/distributed_point_functions_meet_secure_multiparty_computation/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Secure Multiparty Computation allows two or more computing parties to collaboratively compute some function on their (secret) inputs while keeping their inputs secret. MPC has a wide range of applications for privacy-protecting systems. However, unfortunately, the efficiency of MPC protocols is still somewhat limited. Distributed Point Functions (DPFs) are cryptographic primitives allowing us to share a standard-basis vector among two or more parties succinctly. In this talk, we present novel techniques which use DPFs to construct efficient MPC protocols.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Kothapalli made Associate Editor of ACM TOPC    </title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/news/acm_topc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/news/acm_topc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast Multivariate Multipoint Evaluation</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/fast_multivariate_multipoint_evaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/fast_multivariate_multipoint_evaluation/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Multipoint evaluation is the computational task of evaluating a polynomial given as a list of coefficients at a given set of inputs. A straightforward algorithm for this problem is to just iteratively evaluate the polynomial at each of the inputs. The question of obtaining faster-than-naive (and ideally, close to linear time) algorithms for this problem is a natural and fundamental question in computational algebra. In addition to its own inherent interest, faster algorithms for multipoint evaluation are closely related to fast algorithms for other natural algebraic questions like polynomial factorization and modular composition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Godsil type identities of the multi-variate independence polynomials of graphs from heaps theory.</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/godsil_type_identities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/events/theory-seminar/godsil_type_identities/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Given a simple graph G, one can associate a monoid called Cartier–Foata monoid of G (denote it as CF(G)). It is also called trace monoid or partially commutative monoid of G in the literature. Viennot introduced &amp;ldquo;heaps of pieces&amp;rdquo; that give geometric interpretations of elements of CF(G). One can show that the monoid of heaps of pieces in the vertices of G with the concurrency relation determined by G is equivalent to CF(G).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indranil Chakrabarty</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/indranilchakrabarty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/indranilchakrabarty/</guid>
      <description>Testing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kishore Kothapalli</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/kishorekothapalli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/kishorekothapalli/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Information &amp; Computation</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/quantum-information-computation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/quantum-information-computation/</guid>
      <description>As part of CSTAR, we investigate the possibility of making use of quantum mechanics, the physics of fundamental particles, to build computing devices of the future. These machines, known as quantum computers are radically different from their classical counterparts. A major emphasis is given to the design of new algorithms that highlight the differences between classical and quantum computation in the different models of quantum computation. In the near term, we intend to develop algorithms with practical applications for quantum computers that will be available soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samyadeb Bhattacharya</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/samyadebbhattacharya/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/samyadebbhattacharya/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shantanav Chakraborty</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/shantanavchakraborty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/shantanavchakraborty/</guid>
      <description>I have been an Assistant Professor at IIIT Hyderabad since June 2021, where I am affiliated with the Centre for Quantum Science and Technology (CQST) and the Centre for Security, Theory and Algorithmic Research (CSTAR). Prior to this, I was an F.R.S. - FNRS postdoctoral researcher at the Centre for Quantum Information and Communication (QuIC), University libré de Bruxelles, working with Jérémie Roland. I obtained my PhD from the University of Lisbon in December 2017, where I was affiliated with the Physics of Information and QuantumTechnologies Group, supervised by Yasser Omar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standing On The Shoulders Of Srinivasa Ramanujan</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/news/sumit-kumar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/news/sumit-kumar/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suryajith Chillara</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/suryajith.chillara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/people/faculty/suryajith.chillara/</guid>
      <description>Work experience: 08.2021 - present &amp;ndash; Assistant Professor, International Institute of Information Technology, Hyderabad, India. 09.2019 - 08.2021 &amp;ndash; Post Doctoral Fellow at University of Haifa, Israel. 09.2017 - 09.2019 &amp;ndash; Post Doctoral Fellow at Indian Institute of Technology, Bombay, India. Education: 2018 &amp;ndash; Ph.D, Chennai Mathematical Institute, Siruseri, India. 2013 &amp;ndash; M.Sc., Chennai Mathematical Institute, Siruseri, India. 2010 &amp;ndash; B.Tech, Indian Institute of Technology, Kanpur, India.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
