<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Research-areas on CSTAR | IIIT Hyderabad</title>
    <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Research-areas on CSTAR | IIIT Hyderabad</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Algorithms &amp; Complexity</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/algorithms-complexity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/algorithms-complexity/</guid>
      <description>Algorithms are fundamental objects of study in computer science. They are not only the basic building blocks of the computational world around us, but algorithmic processes are ubiquitous in nature too. In this fast-paced world we are not only satisfied with solving a task, but we would like to solve them as fast as possible. The related area of Computational Complexity theory focuses on this issue of computational efficiency. That is, it aims to quantify the amount of computational resources required to solve a given task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distributed &amp; Parallel Computing</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/distributed-parallel-computing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/distributed-parallel-computing/</guid>
      <description>Research in parallel computing took off vigorously in the past two decades with the advent of multi-core and many-core architectures. There is now a renewed interest in designing and engineering efficient parallel algorithms targeted at a multitude of parallel architecture and platforms. Several problems from domains including graph algorithms, natural sciences, optimization, and machine learning are of particular interest owing to their wide range of applications.
Some of the fundamental outcomes of current generation research in parallel computing includes tools for analyzing and modeling GPU computations, techniques for optimizing GPU computations, engineering mechanisms to and algorithms that aim to overlap communication and computation, apart from a host of libraries, domain specific languages, and automatic compiler techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security &amp; Privacy</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/security-privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/security-privacy/</guid>
      <description>Computer security or cybersecurity is the protection of cyber systems and computer networks from the disclosure of information, damage to physical and virtual infrastructure, electronic data, as well as from interruption of the services they provide. The cybersecurity field is becoming important because of the growing dependence on computers, the Internet, wireless communications standards (e.g., Bluetooth and Wi-Fi), as well as the increasing number of &amp;ldquo;smart&amp;rdquo; IoT devices. Due to a variety of reasons, cybersecurity has become one of the major challenges of the modern IT age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theory for Machine Learning</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/theory-for-ml/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/theory-for-ml/</guid>
      <description>In this group, we are interested in theoretical aspects of algorithms that relate specifically to machine learning and related domains such as vision. Some of the research problems consist of designing of better optimization models, solvers and provable guarantee of convergence. Learning part of machine learning often corresponds to minimizing a suitable loss function defined for a labelled data. Hence, optimization methods lies at the center of machine learning research in theory and algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Information &amp; Computation</title>
      <link>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/quantum-information-computation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cstar.iiit.ac.in/research-areas/quantum-information-computation/</guid>
      <description>As part of CSTAR, we investigate the possibility of making use of quantum mechanics, the physics of fundamental particles, to build computing devices of the future. These machines, known as quantum computers are radically different from their classical counterparts. A major emphasis is given to the design of new algorithms that highlight the differences between classical and quantum computation in the different models of quantum computation. In the near term, we intend to develop algorithms with practical applications for quantum computers that will be available soon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
