<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Research-areas on CSTAR | IIIT Hyderabad</title><link>https://cstar-iiit.github.io/research-areas/</link><description>Recent content in Research-areas on CSTAR | IIIT Hyderabad</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cstar-iiit.github.io/research-areas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Algorithms &amp; Complexity</title><link>https://cstar-iiit.github.io/research-areas/algorithms-complexity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cstar-iiit.github.io/research-areas/algorithms-complexity/</guid><description>Testing
sdfds</description></item><item><title>Distributed &amp; Parallel Computing</title><link>https://cstar-iiit.github.io/research-areas/distributed-parallel-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cstar-iiit.github.io/research-areas/distributed-parallel-computing/</guid><description>Testing</description></item><item><title>Security &amp; Privacy</title><link>https://cstar-iiit.github.io/research-areas/security-privacy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cstar-iiit.github.io/research-areas/security-privacy/</guid><description>Computer security or cybersecurity is the protection of cyber systems and computer networks from the disclosure of information, damage to physical and virtual infrastructure, electronic data, as well as from interruption of the services they provide. The cybersecurity field is becoming important because of the growing dependence on computers, the Internet, wireless communications standards (e.g., Bluetooth and Wi-Fi), as well as the increasing number of &amp;ldquo;smart&amp;rdquo; IoT devices. Due to a variety of reasons, cybersecurity has become one of the major challenges of the modern IT age.</description></item><item><title>Theory for Machine Learning</title><link>https://cstar-iiit.github.io/research-areas/theory-for-ml/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 08:47:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cstar-iiit.github.io/research-areas/theory-for-ml/</guid><description>In this group, we are interested in theoretical aspects of algorithms that relate specifically to machine learning and related domains such as vision. Some of the research problems consist of designing of better optimization models, solvers and provable guarantee of convergence. Learning part of machine learning often corresponds to minimizing a suitable loss function defined for a labelled data. Hence, optimization methods lies at the center of machine learning research in theory and algorithms.</description></item><item><title>Quantum Information &amp; Computation</title><link>https://cstar-iiit.github.io/research-areas/quantum-information-computation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cstar-iiit.github.io/research-areas/quantum-information-computation/</guid><description>As part of CSTAR, we investigate the possibility of making use of quantum mechanics, the physics of fundamental particles, to build computing devices of the future. These machines, known as quantum computers are radically different from their classical counterparts. A major emphasis is given to the design of new algorithms that highlight the differences between classical and quantum computation in the different models of quantum computation. In the near term, we intend to develop algorithms with practical applications for quantum computers that will be available soon.</description></item></channel></rss>